[{"question": "  what is that?", "answer": " treeger\u0092s snaking the shower drain.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " what in the name of hell?", "answer": " maybe he found you flip-flop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " whoa! is this porn? what did i do? i must\u0092ve hit something on the remote.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " do we pay for this?", "answer": " no, we didn\u0092t even pay our cable bill\u0097maybe this is how they punish us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " maybe we shouldn\u0092t pay our phone bill\u0097free phone sex.", "answer": " maybe we shouldn\u0092t pay our gas bill?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  whoa, hey, that lady\u0092s all kinds of naked.", "answer": " yeah, joey just pressed something on the remote and it just, came on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " yeah, it happened to me once. i was just flipping through the channels and bam! it was like finding money.", "answer": " like finding money with naked people on it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " all right, y\u0092know what, come on, do we really have to watch this while we eat?  joey and chandler:  oh no-no-no-no!", "answer": " we don\u0092t know what could make this go away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " yeah, so no one touches the remote. and no one touches the tv!", "answer": " and no one touches the air around the tv!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " imagine a protective porn bubble if you will, okay?", "answer": " well at least, i\u0092m going to mute it. joey and chandler: oh no-no-no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " we still have porn.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " honey, what are you doing? that\u0092s too heavy.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " ohh, i\u0092m getting too pregnant for this, lugging around a stupid massage table. y\u0092know, i have to find a job where i carrying a smaller table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " or a job where you don\u0092t have to carry a table.", "answer": " you mean like a doctor?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " pheebs! you\u0092re blocking the porn! look out!", "answer": " ohh!  oh my. oh, that reminds me, i have to see my ob-gyn today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " so uh, emily just went to the airport.", "answer": " oh. why didn\u0092t you take her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " eh, her-her uncle already had planned on doing it. and y\u0092know, we-we said our good-byes this morning, so\u009a", "answer": " you must feel horrible. hey! the guys have free porn!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  nah.", "answer": " hey, cheer up! you\u0092re gonna see her again, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " well i, that\u0092s the thing, i don\u0092t know! i mean, whenever i brought it up with her she said,  \"this is so fantastic! why do we have to talk about the future? let\u0092s just enjoy\u009a\"", "answer": "  no-no-no, don\u0092t-don\u0092t do the accent. you\u0092ve got to see her again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " and why do you care so much?", "answer": " because! you could get to live out my fantasy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " you had fantasies about emily?", "answer": " no! y\u0092know, the fantasy! meet someone from a strange land, fall in madly love, and spend the rest of your lives together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " is that why in junior high you were the only one that hung out with that ukrainian kid?", "answer": " yeah that, plus his mom used to put sour cream on everything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " ahh.", "answer": " do you love her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " we said it was only going to be two weeks, y\u0092know?", "answer": " you love her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " what-what is love really?", "answer": " ohhh, i knew you loved her! then you need to go to the airport and tell her. you\u0092re probably just gonna catch her just as she\u0092s about to go to the gate. you\u0092re gonna call out her name and say, \"i love you!\" and she\u0092s gonna say, \"i love you, too!\" and you guys are going to have the most amazing kiss, everyone at the gate will applaud.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i am a good kisser.", "answer": " then you two can, can sneak into the cockpit, and things will start to heat up, and then a stewardess comes in\u009a  i\u0092ve been watching too much porn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " is that the heartbeat?", "answer": " that\u0092s it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " oh wow! this is so cool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " have we talked about the possibility of multiple births?", "answer": " why don\u0092t take care of this one, and should i get pregnant again, i\u0092ll hold onto your card, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " no, i\u0092m getting three separate heartbeats.", "answer": " three? you guys were worried i wouldn\u0092t even have one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " doctors are wrong all the time.", "answer": " well, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " well, so, are-are you sure that there are three?!", "answer": " definitely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh my god! oh my god! oh my god!! so i-i mean so in a few months i\u0092m going to have three full grown babies just walkin\u0092 around inside me?! oh! oh! and it\u0092s gonna be one of those log rides where they just come shooting out!", "answer": " actually, giving birth to three babies isn\u0092t that different from giving birth to one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  oh-oh, phoebe!", "answer": " ooh! hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " hi!  so, how did it go at the doctors?", "answer": " oh well, okay, hey, y\u0092know how when you\u0092re umm, you\u0092re walking down the street and you see three people in a row, and you say, \"oh, that\u0092s nice?\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " okay, yeah well, good news, you\u0092re going to have three babies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " three babies?", "answer": " i finally got my band!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " we\u0092re gonna have a big family, i\u0092ve always wanted a big family!", "answer": " oh god, i\u0092m so glad you guys are happy, i was so afraid you were going to be all freaked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " why would we be freaked?", "answer": " no, no maybe \u0091cause it\u0092s harder to raise them, and the added expense, and\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  oh.", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " no, back to happy. back to happy!", "answer": " no-no-no, no, it\u0092s going to be fine. because umm, because i teach home ec, and uh, i can have 30 kids making baby clothes all year long. y\u0092know it\u0092ll-it\u0092ll be like my very own little sweatshop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " yeah, i\u0092ve been thinking ever since you said we were having triplets, the best thing for me to do is to drop out of college and get a job.", "answer": " no, frank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " no you can\u0092t quit college! no! you\u0092re in college? really?", "answer": " yeah, refrigerator college.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " yeah, y\u0092know when we found out we were going to have a baby, y\u0092know i figured y\u0092know like i should y\u0092know have like a career\u0097and i love refrigerators!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " you can\u0092t give up on your dream.", "answer": " no, it\u0092s okay. we\u0092re-we\u0092re gonna have three kids! and that\u0092s-that\u0092s a different kind of dream. three kids and no money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  this is the boarding call for flight 009.", "answer": " emily!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i just, i had to see you one more time before you took-off.", "answer": " you are so sweet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " that\u0092s, that\u0092s, that\u0092s a big candy bar.  i had the most amazing time with you.", "answer": " me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " this is the final boarding call for flight 009.", "answer": " well, that\u0092 me.  here, have this.  i\u0092m only allowed one piece of carryon anyway.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  wait uh, listen. i-i, i have to tell you something. umm, i\u0092ve been thinking, i\u0092m just gonna come out and say it. okay? i-i-i ah, i-i think i love you.", "answer": " oh.  thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " what\u0092s that song? it has been in my head all day long.", "answer": " it\u0092s the theme from good will humping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " y\u0092know who doesn\u0092t even like dirty movies? my new boyfriend joshua.", "answer": " yeah right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " no, he told me. he prefers to leave certain things to the imagination.", "answer": " oh-oh, yeah, and did he also say that ah, some of the dialogue was corny and that he actually found it was funny and not sexy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " yeah, he likes porn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " where ya going?", "answer": " i\u0092m going to find out if he really thinks supermodels are too skinny.  hey, pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " how did it go with frank and alice?", "answer": " well, frank has to quit college because his super fertile sister is having three babies! i need to make a lot of money really fast, and i had an idea that i want to talk to you  about, \u0091cause you work for a big company. okay, insider trading, what information is there that you can give me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " ohh! did you do what i said? did-did-did you tell her?", "answer": " i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " and well, what did she say?", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh, you\u0092re totally welcome! what\u0092d she say?", "answer": " she said, \"thank you.\" i said, \"i love you.\" and she said, \"thank you.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " whoa-whoa, wait a minute, did you say, you love her?", "answer": " yeah, what were you trying to get her to do?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " what do i do now?", "answer": " you play hard to get.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " she already lives in london.", "answer": " then you go to tokyo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " all right look, forget it, forget it. you told her you love her, it\u0092s over.", "answer": " it is not over! you\u0092re over!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " okay.  good one.", "answer": " it is not over because she is going to call you and tell you she loves you. and the reason why she couldn\u0092t, is because her feelings were so strong, it scared her. now you go home and wait for her call, she could be calling you from the plane! come on now go! go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi! listen, can we watch cartoons on your television? we need a porn break. we spent the last two hours watching in & out & in, again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " well, so, why don\u0092t you just turn it off?", "answer": " because then we would be the guys who turned off free porn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  ooh, good, you\u0092re hear! okay.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " well, what-what \u0091cha got there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " oh this, well i\u0092m glad you asked.  now, don\u0092t you hate it when you have to cut a tin can with an ordinary steak knife?  ahh! now, i know what you\u0092re thinking\u009a", "answer": " pregnant woman slays four?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " phoebe, they didn\u0092t make you pay for those knives, did they?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " honey, you\u0092re not gonna make enough money to help frank and alice just by selling knives.", "answer": " no-no, i know that, but i just have to make enough money for the second part of my plan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " what\u0092s the second part of your plan?", "answer": " my saturn dealership.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  hello?", "answer": " ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " emily, hi! uh, how-how was you flight?", "answer": " it was dreadful. i felt terrible about how i acted when you said those wonderful things.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " no, no, that-that, that\u0092s all right. umm, i\u0092m just glad you called.", "answer": " ross umm, there\u0092s something that i\u0092ve got to tell you, there\u0092s-there\u0092s someone else.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " she doesn\u0092t know which one of us she wants, me or this colin guy.", "answer": " this isn\u0092t how it\u0092s supposed to go, there can\u0092t be another guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well\u009a", "answer": " of course there\u0092s another guy!! this is even more perfect! now you have to prove your love!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " i\u0092m not proving anything. okay, i\u0092m done listening to you. if i hadn\u0092t let you talk me into going to the airport in the first place, i never would\u0092ve put my fist through the wall!", "answer": " you put your fist through the wall?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " no, i missed and hit the door. but, it opened really hard!", "answer": " you have to go to london!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " yeah, you have to go fight for her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh yeah, sure, that makes sense. yeah. \u0091cause you already told her you love her and she didn\u0092t say it back, then she called you and told you that there\u0092s another guy, so yeah, go to london that\u0092ll scare her!", "answer": " when rachel was with paulo, what did you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i made fun of his accent.", "answer": " you sat back and let him have her, you didn\u0092t fight at all. am i right? do you want the same thing to happen with emily?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " all right then, go fight for her! go to london! i mean, that could be you and emily!  that, but-but nicer. just, go to london!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " come on! surprise her! show up at her doorstep! don\u0092t let her go without a fight!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " all right. all right, i\u0092m gonna do it!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " i\u0092m gonna, i\u0092m gonna go to london and i\u0092m going to fight for her.", "answer": " okay, good luck!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " ooh-ooh! i did it! i did it! i figured out a way to make money! i\u0092m gonna open up my own massage place and frank\u0092s gonna help me! and! we can work it around his schedule so he doesn\u0092t have to quit school!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " that\u0092s sounds great, but how are you going to afford it?", "answer": " well, we were walking down the street and we saw that van that you guys used for catering and we realised\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " i\u0092m telling it! i\u0092m telling it!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay. you know how people need transportation, but they also need massages to help them relax so i just figured we could combine the two, okay, i give the massages and frank drives! i can fix up the van, bolt the table in the back, and you know what i\u0092ve got?", "answer": " a place where no one will ever get out alive?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " no! think about it, it\u0092s a taxi that people take when they need to relax, it\u0092s\u009a", "answer": "  relaxi-taxi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " the name was my favourite part!", "answer": " well, well i can up with it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " you did not!!!! oh! no! you came up with relaxi cab! that\u0092s not good.", "answer": " well, i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " no, because she hasn\u0092t come home yet. and she hasn\u0092t been home all night! she\u0092s obviously staying with that other guy, and i\u0092m the stupid moron who spent the whole night outside her apartment!", "answer": " all right. when is, when is the next flight out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " about four hours.", "answer": " okay, just stay there a couple more hours and if she doesn\u0092t show up by then, then just come on home.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " hey, tell him about relaxi-taxi, and-and ask him if he thinks that\u0092s better than relaxi cab.", "answer": " okay, it\u0092s not relaxi cab. it\u0092s relaxicab, like taxicab.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " are we in london?", "answer": " what are you doing here? you can\u0092t be here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " what?", "answer": "  nothing. no, nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " i was going to call him, but\u009a", "answer": " oh, you came to tell him you love him! i knew it!  i was right!  i\u0092m right, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " i\u0092d really rather talk to him.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " ross, are you there? ross, i don\u0092t know if you can hear this but\u009a  i\u0092m gonna talk anyway, uh, i\u0092m in the states with you sister and your friends and it\u0092s all over with colin. i came here to tell you that, and to tell you\u0097yes, joey you can have all the chocolate you want, just take it! uh, i came here to tell you that i love you.", "answer": "  i love you too! i\u0092m, i\u0092m gonna call you right now from the phone booth!  you can\u0092t hear me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " i wish i could know if you\u0092d heard any of that. i suppose i\u0092ve either just told you i love you or given my neighbours a good laugh. mrs. newman if you\u0092re listening, bugger off this in none of your business. i suppose there\u0092s not much chance you did heard that, and there\u0092s the call waiting so, i should go. oh well.  hello.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " ross, i love you!", "answer": " ohh! thank you. closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i was just at the bank, and there was this really hot teller, and she didn\u0092t ask me to go do it with her in the vault.", "answer": " same kind of thing happened to me! woman pizza delivery guy come over, gives me the pizza, takes the money, and leaves!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " what, no, \"nice apartment, i bet the bedrooms are huge?\"", "answer": " noo! nothing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " y\u0092know what, we have to turn off the porn.", "answer": " i think you\u0092re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " all right, ready?", "answer": " one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " two.", "answer": " three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " that\u0092s kinda nice.", "answer": " yeah, that\u0092s kinda a relief.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " you wanna see if we still have it?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " free porn!!!", "answer": " yeah!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}]